Notice how the body is now seen from a distance.
The body is there, in front.
Where are you?
No need to decide.
Just notice.
Now I would like you to move parts of your body and to simply observe.
Please raise your right hand and make small regular movements up and down.
Right and left, slowly.
Notice how the body moves.
Now place your right hand on your left shoulder.
Observe.
Now, please raise your left hand and make small regular movements.
Up and down.
Right and left, slowly.
Now, place your left hand on your right shoulder.
Notice how the body moves.
Now move your right hand to your lap and then move your left hand to your lap.
Rest like this for a moment.
Where are you at the location of the body you see, at the location from where you see,
somewhere else?
Again, just notice and stay in this state.